One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
No!
Olamaz!
Listen, Nami.
Unutma Nami,
Using the Climate Baton in battle starts with using your head!
İklim Asası, gücünü senin zekândan alır.
Keep your wits about you to survive!
Hayatta kalmak için aklını kullan!
That's our true weapon after all.
Sonuçta bizim asıl silahımız bu.
Heat balls and cool balls...
Isı ve soğuk kabarcıklarını...
Combining them makes full use of their attributes!
birleştirerek özelliklerinden tam yararlanabilirim!
That's the power of the Climate Baton!
İklim Asası'nın gücü bu!
And one last thing:
Ve son olarak,
Tornado Tempo! It's this weapon's flagship move!
Hortum Tempo! Bu silahın imza hareketi!
Tornado Tempo...
Hortum Tempo...
As long as your opponent is human, they won't be standing after getting hit.
Karşındaki insan olduğu müddetçe, bu saldırıyı yedikten sonra ayakta duramaz!
But you only get one shot, so use it as a last resort.
Ama sadece tek hakkın var, bu yüzden dikkat et!
If you miss, consider it over.
Kaçırırsan, her şey biter!
If I miss, it's over...
Kaçırırsam, her şey biter.
Pay attention.
Dikkatini ver.
Interesting weapon you've got there...
Epey ilginç bir silahın var.
But without effective attacks, isn't it just a toy?
Ama dövüşürken sana yardımcı olmazsa, oyuncaktan farkı yoktur, değil mi?
Its original design doesn't matter. It's a only a weapon... when...
Asıl amacı ne olursa olsun, insan öldürmek için kullanılabilecek her şey bir silahtır.
it harms someone.
Yüz bile...
If I don't hurry up, I'll be killed...
Böyle oyalanıp durursam öleceğim!
The final, most powerful technique... Tornado Tempo... I need to be quick!
Son ve en güçlü teknik... Hortum Tempo... Hızlı olmalıyım!
G-Give that back!
G-Geri ver!
You can't kill me with a toy like this.
Bu küçük oyuncak tarafından öldürülemem.
A sweater could build up a better charge than this.
Bahse varım yün kazak bundan daha fazla elektrik üretirdi.
We won't know until I try!
Ben yapana dek bilemezsin!
Give it back to me!
Ver şunu!
Think!
Düşünmeliyim.
If I lower her guard, she can't dodge the one-shot attack, Tornado Tempo!
Gardını düşürürsem, tek atışlık saldırı olan Hortum Tempo'dan kaçamaz!
It might work!
Sanırım...!
Three types of air bubbles...
Üç çeşit baloncuğu ve...
Is there some way to use them in this country's parched climate?
bu ülkenin kuru iklimini birleştirerek ne yapabilirim?
If only there was a little more moisture in the air!
Havada birazcık daha nem olsaydı...
Moisture... That's right! If I remember correctly, there's a rain technique...
Nem... Tabii ya! Yağmur tekniği vardı!
Rain Tempo!
Yağmur Tempo!
Water tricks, huh?
Su numaraları, ha?
Sprinkler!
Fıskiye!
You seem desperate.
Umutsuz vakasın.
No! I have a plan!
Hayır, lanet olası! Bir planım var!
Enough already. You can stop with the parlor tricks.
Yeter artık. Bu gösteri işi eskidi.
The party is at its height. Let's call it quits.
Perdeyi kapama zamanı geldi!
A sea urchin?!
Deniz kestanesi mi?!
Sea Urchin Stinger!
Deniz Kestanesi Dikeni!
I'll poke you full of holes!
Seni delik deşik edeceğim!
So much for poking holes... She incinerated the wall!
Delik açmakla kalmadı... Duvarı yakıp kül etti!
You put on a great show earlier, so allow me to return the favor.
Önceki performansın harikaydı, şimdi ben de karşılık vereyim.
Now's my chance!
İşte fırsat!
Heat Ball!
Isı Kabarcığı!
Hot air rises while absorbing moisture.
Nemli sıcak hava yükselip...
It rapidly cools when it hits descending cold air, freezing the moisture.
alçalan soğuk havayla çarçabuk soğuduğunda, içindeki nem yoğunlaşacak.
That's when...
Sonra da...
Spike-Spike Doping!
Diken-Diken Doping!
I said pay attention, didn't I?!
Dikkatini ver, dememiş miydim?
Stinger Flail!
Dikenli Topuz!
My goodness. I suppose you're at least an expert in running away.
Cidden, iyi olduğun tek şey kaçmak gibi duruyor tatlım.
Right! The air bubbles!
Tabii ya! Baloncuklar!
It formed!
Oluşmuş!
It's small, but it's a cloud alright!
Biraz küçük ama bulut yaptım!
What the hell?
Neden bahsediyorsun?
Not enough. It needs to be bigger!
Yetmez. Daha büyük yapmalıyım!
Cool Ball!
Soğuk Kabarcığı!
Heat Ball!
Isı Kabarcığı!
That's enough out of you!
Yeter artık!
You wretched little...!
Ulan...!
Stinger Flail!
Dikenli Topuz!
So? Are you ready to die?
Ee? Ölmeye hazır mısın?
Are you?
Peki ya sen?
Bluffing, I see.
Blöfünü görüyorum.
Got you.
Yakaladım.
You'll pay for that!
Affedilemez!
What?!
Ne?!
For today's weather,
Bugünkü hava durumunda...
the wind and humidity are both stable,
rüzgâr ve nem dengeli,
and we have a high pressure system on this fine, sunny day.
güzel, güneşli bir gün için yüksek basınç hakim.
However, in one particular area, you may find mirages and cyclones.
Ancak belli bir bölgede, seraplar ve kasırgalar görebilirsiniz.
Be on the lookout for tornadoes.
Hortumlara dikkat edin!
Tornado Tempo! It's this weapon's flagship move!
Hortum Tempo! Bu silahın imza hareketi!
But you only get one shot, so use it as a last resort.
Ama sadece tek hakkın var, bu yüzden dikkat et!
If you miss, consider it over.
Kaçırırsan, her şey biter!
If I miss, it's over...
Kaçırırsam... her şey biter.
Beware of twisters!
Hortumlara dikkat!
Are you okay?
İyi misin?
Your left leg has taken a lot of punishment.
Sol bacağın sana epey acı çektiriyor.
You won't be able to stand for much longer.
Daha fazla ayakta duramayacaksın.
Sea Urchin Stinger!
Deniz Kestanesi Dikeni!
This is... nothing...!
Bu... hiçbir şey!
It doesn't hurt at all!
Hiç acımıyor!
Don't you know how much she's suffered?!
Onun neler çektiğini biliyor musun?!
Compared to her pain...
Onunla karşılaştırıldığında,
a leg or two, or three...
bir, iki veya üç bacağı feda etmek,
don't mean a thing!
hiç önemli değil!!!
This is it!
Al bunu.
Tornado Tempo!
Hortum Tempo!
Huh?
Ha?
Wha...? What? Wh-What in the world?!
N...? Ne? N-Ne oluyor be?!
The doves wrapped around me!
Güvercinler bana dolandı!
Ow...
Ah...
I did it... I did it! Usopp... Vivi...!
Başardım... Ben başardım! Usopp... Vivi...!
What is he talking about? Pluton? What in the world is he...?
Neden bahsediyor? Pluton nedir? Ne planlıyor...?
I hear that one shot from Pluton can completely destroy an island.
Duyduğum kadarıyla, Pluton'un tek atışıyla bir ada yok olabilirmiş.
Named after a god, it was antiquity's most devastating weapon.
Tanrı adını taşıyan, dünyadaki en korkunç antik silah.
It should be hidden somewhere in this country.
Ve bu ülkede bir yerde sessizce uyuyor.
An ancient weapon? Such a thing exists here...
Antik bir silah mı? Bu ülkede mi?
and my father knew?
Babam biliyor muydu?
A secret passed down with the throne...
Kraliyet ailesinde nesilden nesile geçen sır.
That's been my target from the start.
Başından beri amacım buydu.
With it, I'll build a state with the most fearsome military right here.
Bunu kullanarak, burada en korkutucu orduya sahip bir devlet kuracağım.
That's been your aim all this time?!
Öyleyse yaptığın her şey bu amaç için miydi?!
Once I become the king,
Bu ülkenin kralı olduğum zaman,
I'll easily draw the local pirates under my umbrella,
bölgedeki korsanları kolayca kontrolüm altına alabilirim.
expanding my influence until I can best the World Government.
Güç kazanırken, Dünya Hükûmeti'nden bile üstün olacağım.
This will be a country of dreams!
Burası hayaller ülkesi olacak!
Impossible! The World Government will not stand for it!
İmkânsız! Dünya Hükûmeti buna izin vermez!
They probably won't, which is precisely why I need Pluton.
Biliyorum, bu yüzden Pluton'a ihtiyacım var.
I don't know where you could have heard that name,
O ismi nereden duyduğunu bilmiyorum ama,
but I don't know its location.
nerede olduğu hakkında bir fikrim yok.
I cannot even verify if it truly exists somewhere in this land.
Hatta bu krallıkta böyle bir şey var mı emin değilim!
I see. What you say probably isn't a complete lie...
Anlıyorum. Durumun böyle olacağını düşünmüştüm.
and I feared that might be the case.
Bu olasılığı zaten hesaplamıştım.
Even I know that its very existence remains in doubt.
Varlığının belirsizliği, benim tarafımdan bile reddedilemez.
What noisy flies...
Ne gürültücü sinekler...
I heard that Crocodile crucified King Cobra.
Crocodile, Cobra-sama'yı içeride rehin tutuyor!
Save His Majesty!
Cobra-sama'yı kurtarmalıyız!
We have to find a way inside at any cost!
Ne olursa olsun bir yol bulup içeri girmeliyiz!
But those hands sprouting from the door are keeping us out!
Ama kapıdan çıkmış o eller varken, kırıp giremiyoruz!
We're stuck until we do something about them!
Onları halletmeden ilerleyemeyiz!
Just as I had planned,
Her şey plana göre giderse,
the Rebel Army will reach that square in twenty minutes and start fighting.
İsyan Ordusu 20 dakika içinde meydana ulaşacak ve savaş başlayacak.
And then—that is to say, 30 minutes from now at 4:30—
Yarım saat sonra, tam olarak 4:30'da,
I've ordered a powerful blast aimed at the square.
meydana doğru çok güçlü bir top ateşlenecek.
Are you insane?!
Delirdin mi sen?!
It's designed to level anything within five kilometers.
Top, beş kilometre çapında bir patlama oluşturacak.
The view from here will greatly change.
Güzel manzaranız tamamen değişecek.
If you do that...!
Bunu yaparsan...!
No one from either the Royal Army or the Rebel Army will survive.
Hem Kraliyet Ordusu hem de İsyan Ordusu yok edilecek.
Hence, the battle will cease permanently.
Düşecekler ve savaşları sonsuza dek bitmiş olacak.
Doesn't that please you? After all, you wanted so badly to stop them.
Mutlu olmalısın. Bu isyanın sona erişini görmek için çok çalıştın.
Instead of meticulously trying to blow up the palace,
Sarayı yok etmek dolaylı bir yoldu.
you'll reach your goal quicker by just blowing up both armies.
Bir çırpıda herkesi yok etmek, çok daha verimli.
How can you do such a thing?!
Bunu nasıl yapabilirsin?!
What could they have done to deserve this kind of fate?!
Bu kaderi hak edecek ne yapmış olabilirler?!
You are... You are...
Sen... Sen...
Your Highness...!
Vivi-sama!
They're worthless.
Onlar değersiz.
Please stop this! What good will come of it?
Kes şunu! Bunu yaparak ne elde edebilirsin ki?
Princess Vivi!
Vivi-sama!
Now, Mr. Cobra. Let me ask you another question.
Şimdi, Bay Cobra. Başka bir soru soracağım.
Where can I find the poneglyph?
Poneglif nerede?
Poneglyph... Why would you need...?
Poneglif... Neden ihtiyacın olsun ki...?
If I tell you where it is...
Nerede olduğunu söylersem...
No... I'll show you.
Hayır... Seni oraya götüreceğim.
Papa...
Baba...
That's the wise King Cobra for you! You're a clever man.
Bilge hükümdar Cobra'dan da bu beklenirdi. Akıllı bir adamsın.
Your Highness!
Vivi-sama.
I can't... take this any more!
Artık buna dayanamıyorum!
I'll show you... the difference in pride...
Sana kılıçlarımız arasındaki gurur farkını...
between your swords and mine!
göstereceğim!
Three-Sword Style...
Üç Kılıç Stili...
Bull...
Boğa...
Spines!
Boynuzu!
Spider...
Demir Gard...
So basically, your body is hard as steel.
Demek bedenin çelik kadar sert.
If I can't cut steel, then I can't cut you, huh?
Çeliği kesemezsem, seni de kesemem.
That would be correct.
Dediğin gibi.
Smashing and cutting attacks don't work on me.
Vurma ve kesme saldırıları beni etkilemeyecek.
I admit, this one's a toughie.
Anlıyorum. Bu çok can sıkıcı.
Since I'm not yet capable of cutting steel, I can't defeat you now.
Çeliği kesemediğime göre, seni yenemem.
Then what's your next move?
Peki, ne yapacaksın?
Simple. I'll give you my sympathy.
Basit. Senin adına üzüldüm.
What?
Ne?
I've been looking forward to an obstacle like this.
Böyle zor bir durum, tam da ihtiyacım olan şeydi.
I was thinking that it's high time I reached the next level.
Bir adım daha güçlenmek için fırsat arıyordum.
When I defeat you,
Seni yendiğim zaman,
I'll be a man who can even cut steel.
çeliği kesebilen bir adam olacağım.
When you defeat me, huh?
Beni yendiğin zaman mı?
You might want to curb your enthusiasm.
Heyecanını biraz frenlesen iyi olur.
Just know that ever since I gained my Dice-Dice powers,
Bil ki, Kesme Meyvesi yediğimden beri,
not a single so-called swordsman has so much as scratched me.
hiçbir sözde kılıç ustası bana tek bir çizik bile atamadı.
Those who wield swords... are powerless before me.
Bir kılıç ustası olarak, beni yenemezsin.
Yeah, I get the picture.
Evet, ne dediğini anlıyorum,
Then we can go ahead and close the book on those tales of yours.
ama o güzel anıları albümün için saklamalısın.
I don't know how many swordsmen you've fought in the past,
Geçmişte kaç tane kılıç ustasıyla dövüştüğün önemli değil.
but you and I are meeting for the first time.
Benimle hiç karşılaşmadın.
It seems that at least your tongue is sharp.
En azından dilin keskin.
Thanks, baldy.
Teşekkürler, keltoş.
We'll see how long you'll last.
Bakalım ne kadar dayanacaksın.
Right back at you.
Sana bağlı.
Oni...
İblis...
Giri!
Kesişi!
Tiger...
Kaplan...
Trap!
Avı!
I told you, didn't I?
Sana söylemiştim, değil mi?
It's a little shocking that you didn't even get a single bruise...
Tek bir çizik bile yok. Moral bozucu.
And I've never seen an opponent still standing after solid hits like that.
Bu kadar güç kullanmamın ardından, ilk kez birinin ayağa kalktığını görüyorum.
Of course you haven't.
Elbette.
After all, we're meeting for the first time.
Daha önce benimle hiç karşılaşmadın.
That's right!
Doğru!
This guy's a human blade.
Bu herif kılıç adam.
Every part of his body is a cutting edge!
Vücudunun her bir parçası keskin.
Sparkling Daisy!
Papatya Bıçağı!
H-He's...
B-Bu adam...
Begone.
Uçup git.
I train harder than anyone I know.
Kendimi herkesten fazla zorladım.
I've had to face my limitations in many difficult situations before.
Defalarca kez ölümün eşiğine geldim.
What is it that I lack?!
Bende eksik olan şey ne?!
Sensei...! Sensei!
Sensei...! Sensei!
Hmm?
Hmm?
There are men in this world who can cut through anything? Even steel?
Dünyada çeliği bile kesebilen adamlar olduğunu duydum!
Is that true?!
Bu doğru mu?!
Yes, it's true.
Evet, doğru.
Now, watch this paper carefully, Zoro.
Hazır mısın? Kağıdı dikkatle izle, Zoro.
Sensei, you didn't cut it.
Sensei, kağıt hâlâ tek parça.
Listen well, Zoro.
İyi dinle, Zoro.
There are swordsmen out there who are capable of cutting nothing.
Yaşadığımız dünyada, hiçbir şeyi kesemeyen kılıç ustaları vardır.
But they can also cut anything, even steel—using the very same blade.
Ve aynı kılıç ustaları, aynı kılıçla çeliği veya istedikleri her şeyi kesebilir.
The height of swordsmanship is protecting exactly what one wishes to protect
Kılıç ustalığının zirvesi, korumak istediğini koruma...
and cutting exactly what one wishes to cut.
kesmek istediğini kesme gücüdür.
A blade that injures all that it touches...
Dokunduğu her şeye zarar veren bir kılıç,
Well, to me, that isn't true swordsmanship.
bana göre, gerçek bir kılıç değildir.
Do you understand?
Anlıyor musun?
Sensei, I'll be a swordsman who can cut anything!
Sensei, her şeyi kesebilen bir kılıç ustası olacağım!
Zoro, did you hear a word I said?
Zoro, söylediklerimi duymadın mı?
See if you can nick me already.
Beni kesmeyi denemelisin.
You'll never scratch me if you're always on the defensive.
Sadece saldırılarımı karşılamak, bedenimi çizmeyecek.
Unfortunately, you'll never get to see me as I resolutely cut steel...
Ne yazık ki, çeliği kararlılıkla kesişimi asla göremeyeceksin…
because when I do cut steel, that's when you'll be dead.
Çünkü çeliği kestiğim an, ayak ucumda yattığın an olacak.
So you say.
Mantıklı...
I'll cut anything and everything... into pieces!
Öyleyse, buradaki her şeyi atomlarına dek keseceğim!
"Swordsmen capable of cutting nothing," huh?
"Hiçbir şeyi kesmeyen kılıç," ha?
Cut nothing... but also cut steel.
Hiçbir şeyi kesmeyen... Çeliği kesen...
I don't understand what it means at all!
Bunun ne anlama gelmesi gerekiyor?!
Keep thrusting onward! That's the secret to a more powerful sword!
Tüm gücünle zorla! Güçlü bir kılıcın özü budur!
Atomic Spar!
Atom Kesici!
I'll just cut you up!
Seni doğrayacağım!
Crab... Grab!
Yengeç Kapışı!
I've about had it with this guy.
Sinir bozucu birisin.
The feeling is mutual.
Sen de öylesin.
Let me tell you one thing. Do not consider me a swordsman.
Bir tavsiye. Beni bir kılıç ustası olarak görme.
I am full of weapons that can dice you into pieces.
Bedenini parçalama kapasitesine sahip çok sayıda silahım var.
Spiral Hollow!
Sarmal Testere!
Not a swordsman... So then you're an excavator?!
Kılıç ustası değilsen, belki de kazıcısındır.
I'm an assassin!
Suikastçıyım.
Sparks?! Just how fast is he spinning?!
Kıvılcım mı?! Ne kadar hızlı dönüyorlar?!
I can't hold it...!
Tutamıyorum...
I could never be an excavator. I'd pulverize anything I touch.
Kazma işi benim için imkânsız. Dokunduğum her şeyi un ufak ederim.
Crap!
Kahretsin!
A moment's miscalculation invites...
Anlık yanlış hesaplama, ölüme...
death!
yol açar!
You're still breathing...
Hâlâ nefes alıyorsun...
I can't turn my back to him...!
Ona sırtımı dönemem!
Why keep struggling when you're disarmed?
Çıplak ellerinle nasıl mücadele edeceksin?
Spar Break!
Kule Parçalayıcı!
Rest in peace.
Huzur içinde öl.
Today...
Bugün...
is not my day for stone.
taşlardan yana şansım kötü.
The others... I wonder if they're okay.
Diğerleri iyi mi... merak ediyorum.
How are you still standing? I sliced you to shreds.
Hâlâ nasıl ayakta durabilirsin? Seni lime lime ettim.
Did you dodge all of those falling stones?
Düşen taşları nasıl savuşturabildin?
These stones... Did I dodge them?
Taşları... savuşturdum mu?
No...
Hayır, öyle olmadı.
I knew... where the stones would land.
Taşların düşmeyeceği yeri biliyordum.
One of my swords...
Kılıçlarımdan biri...
is there, under that stone.
o taşın altında.
I can tell.
Biliyorum.
What's he doing...?
Ne yapıyor bu?
I've experienced this feeling before.
Daha önce de böyle hissetmiştim.
Everything goes silent around me.
Etrafımda her şey sessizleşiyor.
I become keenly aware of my own heartbeat.
Kulaklarımda yankılanan kalp atışımı duyabiliyorum.
It's as if... I'm standing close to the gates of hell.
Cehennemin kapılarında duruyormuşum gibi.
When the stones were falling, I could sense them as if they were alive.
Düşen taşların varlığını canlı şeylermiş gibi hissettim.
No, I didn't sense them... It was more distinct than that.
Ama varlık olarak değil daha başka bir şekilde.
Rhythm...
Nefes...
A stone's... rhythm.
Nefes alan taşlar...
Trees have their own rhythm.
Nefes alan ağaçlar...
Even the soil has its own. Is that what this is?
Nefes alan yeryüzü... Bu mu?
Listen well.
İyi dinle.
There are swordsmen out there who are capable of cutting nothing.
Yaşadığımız dünyada, hiçbir şeyi kesemeyen kılıç ustaları vardır.
When cutting nothing...
Hiçbir şeyi kesememek,
Is that knowing the rhythm?
o nefesi duymak mıdır?
Is this... the power to cut even steel?
Bu... çeliği kesme gücü mü?
You... How did you manage this?
Lanet olası... Ne yaptın sen?!
You received a debilitating blow, and you're drenched in your own blood...
O yaraları aldıktan sonra, o kadar kan kaybettikten sonra,
There's no way you can still be alive!
yaşıyor olamazsın!
I can hear... the rhythm of his steel...
Onu duyabiliyorum. Çeliğinin nefesini.
My sword is an extension of my will.
Kılıcım, irademin bir uzantısıdır.
Fine. You'll be dead for sure after this next attack.
Peki öyleyse. Hayatına tamamen son vereceğim!
All that's left...
Geriye,
is to see for sure if I gained the ability to cut steel.
çeliği kesecek güce sahip olup olmadığımı görmek kaldı.
So you believe one sword can defend against this attack.
Saldırılarımı tek bir kılıçla karşılayamazsın.
Don't worry. I won't defend again.
Sorun değil. Artık onları karşılamayacağım.
So you've accepted your fate. Fine by me!
Demek kendini hazırladın. Bana uyar.
One-Sword Style Draw...
Tek Kılıç Stili!
Lion Song!
Aslan Şarkısı!
Atomic Spurt!
Atom Kesici!
I give you my thanks.
Minnettarım.
I can get stronger still!
Hâlâ daha güçlü olabilirim!
He really did... get stronger... during this fight...
Gerçekten, bu dövüş içerisinde kendi sınırını aştı.
What's next...?
Sırada...
Are you going to cut diamond...?
elmas kesmek mi var?
That would be a waste.
Zaman kaybı olurdu.
You win...
Canıma okudun.
Battle Behind the Medi Assembly Hall
Alubarna Kuzey Bloğu
Alubarna North Block
Medi Toplantı Salonunun Arka Caddesindeki Dövüş
Winner: Nami
Kazanan: Nami
Medi Assembly Hall, Main Street North Block
Kuzey Bloğu Medi Toplantı Salonu, Ana Cadde
Battle in Front of the Medi Assembly Hall
Alubarna Kuzey Bloğu
Alubarna North Block
Medi Toplantı Salonu Ana Cadde Dövüşü
Winner: Zoro
Kazanan: Zoro